At the beginning of the course, I told
you I was only going to teach you um
prompt alert and console.log. Um that
was so that you could focus on learning
how to do the most important part of
programming, which is how to do the
logical work that we are now at a
pivotal moment because we are now
transitioning from how to do the
underlying logic of the program like
writing functions and if statements and
we're going to transition a little more
into how to work with more inputs and
outputs. So, what we're going to do is
we're going to start editing the HTML
page. We're going to start getting input
from outside of our HTML page. And all
of that is going to start from just
about now. Um,
so you're going to find yourself using a
lot of functions, accessing a lot of
attributes of objects, and working with
a lot of arrays. If any of that is
uncomfortable for you, you may want to
review previous videos. Um, but I'm
excited because this is where things
start to get